Today a food poisoning took me straight to God.
Oh, I mean,
after visiting Prem Mandir last night, we got a little too
wrapped up in anticipation.
Due to which I got food poisoning in my intestines by
morning.  It seemed that
Chitragupta ji might ask for my face verification now.
But today we had to
leave for Rajasthan somehow.  So I
managed with mint etc.  As we kept moving forward,
my health kept getting better
because I was very excited to go to
Barsana and people say that out of all the people who
come to Vrindavan, only a
few are able to go to Barsana. I too am
coming to Vrindavan for the third time and going to Barsana for the first time,
but I had no idea that Ladli ji's
temple would be at such a height. Firstly, I was
unwell and I was not sure whether I would be able to climb so many stairs. With
this fear, I kept moving forward,
but it is said that devotion has a lot of power.
I reached the temple premises,
I applied tilak etc. and
met you all too. Then my friend Varsha, Buddha Dev
ji and Mota Bhai had also applied tilak. So
we moved towards the temple and there was so much crowd here
that after having darshan, we started looking at the view outside
and while coming back, such a
monkey's spirit came inside me that by jumping I
reached straight to the earth.  So now
people of Rajasthan, control your hearts.  We are coming
Radhe-Radhe.